import { Game } from "../model/game";
export const HouseChurchGame: Game = {
    round1: [
        {
            title: "We Love the 90s",
            questions: [
                {
                    value: 100,
                    question: "In 2019, a judge ruled that this popular 90s dance from the show 'Fresh Prince of Bel-Air' could not be copyrighted",
                    answer: "The Carlton Dance"
                },
                {
                    value: 200,
                    question: "This 1997 film was the first to gross over 1 billion dollars worldwide",
                    answer: "The Titanic"
                },
                {
                    value: 300,
                    question: "This was the name of the world's first cloned mammal, introduced to the world in 1996",
                    answer: "Dolly the Sheep"
                },
                {
                    value: 400,
                    question: "Ryan Gosling, Britney Spears, and Justin Timberlake were all members of this Disney variety show featuring comedic sketches and music videos",
                    answer: "The Mickey Mouse Club"
                },
                {
                    value: 500,
                    question: "This iconic shoe featured inflatable chambers for a better fit and was worn by Allen Iverson, Yao Ming, and Shaquille O'Neal",
                    answer: "Reebok Pumps"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            title: "Weird Animal Facts",
            questions: [
                {
                    value: 100,
                    question: "This animal has the highest blood pressure of any animal in order to pump blood to its extremely long limbs",
                    answer: "Giraffe"
                },
                {
                    value: 200,
                    question: "The average elephant weighs less than the tongue of this giant species of whale",
                    answer: "Blue whale"
                },
                {
                    value: 300,
                    question: "Due to it's corkscrew shape, this animal holds the proud distinction of having the largest penis length relative to its weight",
                    answer: "Duck"
                },
                {
                    value: 400,
                    question: "This animal's jaws generate enough force to crush a bowling ball, yet could not kill Leonardo DiCaprio in the Revenant",
                    answer: "Grizzly Bear"
                },
                {
                    value: 500,
                    question: "This animal uses rocks as tools, and have been known to keep the same 'favorite' rock with them for their entire lifetime",
                    answer: "Otters"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            title: "Music",
            questions: [
                {
                    value: 100,
                    question: "Justin Timberlake was the lead singer of what famous boy band",
                    answer: "NSYNC"
                },
                {
                    value: 200,
                    question: "Every year, this duo plays a special concert at the the Fixer Upper's Silobration",
                    answer: "Johnny Swim"
                },
                {
                    value: 300,
                    question: "In 2011, this star suffered a vocal chord hemorrhage shortly after the release of the Album '21'",
                    answer: "Adele"
                },
                {
                    value: 400,
                    question: "In 2016, this Rock and Roll Hall of Fame artist died of a fentanyl overdose in his Minnesota home",
                    answer: "Prince"
                },
                {
                    value: 500,
                    question: "This Buggles song was the first music video to be played on MTV",
                    answer: "Video Killed the Radio Star"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            title: "Sports",
            questions: [
                {
                    value: 100,
                    question: "This city has hosted the First Four every year since its inception in 2011",
                    answer: "Dayton"
                },
                {
                    value: 200,
                    question: "This was the only player to win two Heisman Trophies",
                    answer: "Archie Griffin"
                },
                {
                    value: 300,
                    question: "In 1976, this was the last team to finish its college basketball season undefeated",
                    answer: "Indiana Hoosiers"
                },
                {
                    value: 400,
                    question: "In the 2006 World Cup, this French soccer player received a redcard in his final career game for headbutting another player",
                    answer: "Zinedine Zidane"
                },
                {
                    value: 500,
                    question: "In 2008, Michael Phelps broke this swimmer's record of most medals in a single Olympics",
                    answer: "Mark Spitz"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            title: "Feeling Presidential",
            questions: [
                {
                    value: 100,
                    question: "This is the only president to have been elected more than twice",
                    answer: "FDR"
                },
                {
                    value: 200,
                    question: "This was the first U.S. President to live in the White House",
                    answer: "John Adams"
                },
                {
                    value: 300,
                    question: "The 11th President oversaw the acquisition of the Oregon Territory in 1848",
                    answer: "James K Polk"
                },
                {
                    value: 400,
                    question: "This state holds the distinction of having the most presidents born there",
                    answer: "Virginia"
                },
                {
                    value: 500,
                    question: "The Chicago Daily Tribune mistakenly ran a headline stating that Thomas Dewey had beaten this candidate, who had actually won",
                    answer: "Harry S Truman"
                }
            ]
        }
    ],
    round2: [
        {
            title: "Board Game Geeks",
            questions: [
                {
                    value: 200,
                    question: "In this board game you receive 2 victory points for having the longest road",
                    answer: "Settler's of Catan"
                },
                {
                    value: 400,
                    question: "What restaurants cups did Michael Ramsey's house place all over the floor of our apartment, preventing us from leaving our rooms",
                    answer: "McDonald's"
                },
                {
                    value: 600,
                    question: "What object did Brink grab when Josh threw Mark up against a wall in his sleep",
                    answer: "Golf club"
                },
                {
                    value: 800,
                    question: "What is the name of the victim in the board game Clue",
                    answer: "Mr Boddy"
                },
                {
                    value: 1000,
                    question: "During Cinco de mayo festivities, what did Josh use to hold up the pinata",
                    answer: "A crutch"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            title: "NCAA Name Game",
            questions: [
                {
                    value: 200,
                    question: "What is the name of Miami University's Redhawk mascot",
                    answer: "Swoop"
                },
                {
                    value: 400,
                    question: "This university is the only division 1 school with a fruit as its mascot",
                    answer: "Syracuse University"
                },
                {
                    value: 600,
                    question: "This state's school of design is located in Providence, and their mascot is 'Scrotie the Nads', a giant walking penis",
                    answer: "Rhode Island"
                },
                {
                    value: 800,
                    question: "In 1997, these two universities sharing the nickname 'Wildcats' played each other for the NCAA Basketball Championship",
                    answer: "Arizona and Kentucky"
                },
                {
                    value: 1000,
                    question: "The University of California - Santa Cruz's mascot is named after this gastropod, one of the slowest on earth, moving at a maximum speed of six inches per minute",
                    answer: "Banana Slug"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            title: "Brotherly Love",
            questions: [
                {
                    value: 200,
                    question: "These Spanish brothers have a combined 9 all star games between them",
                    answer: "Pao and Marc Gasol"
                },
                {
                    value: 400,
                    question: "These two brothers are both in the top 10 of career 3 point percentage",
                    answer: "Seth and Steph Curry"
                },
                {
                    value: 600,
                    // tslint:disable-next-line: max-line-length
                    question: "These 3 Duke players were the first trio of brothers in the NBA since the Barry brothers",
                    answer: "Marshall, Mason, and Miles"
                },
                {
                    value: 800,
                    question: "This brother and sister duo are the only ones to both be in the Basketball Hall of Fame",
                    answer: "Reggie and Cheryl Miller"
                },
                {
                    value: 1000,
                    question: "In 2014, the Phoenix Suns had two different pairs of brothers on their team; name them",
                    answer: "Marcus and Markieff Morris, and Zoran and Goran Dragic"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            title: "I Love the 90s",
            questions: [
                {
                    value: 200,
                    question: "This shot-blocking center was known for his trademark finger-wag",
                    answer: "Dikembe Mutumbo"
                },
                {
                    value: 400,
                    question: "This 7'6\" center had his powers stolen from him in Space Jam",
                    answer: "Shawn Bradley"
                },
                {
                    value: 600,
                    question: "Known as the Round Mound of Rebound, this player was awful at golf",
                    answer: "Charles Barkley"
                },
                {
                    value: 800,
                    question: "The 1997 number 1 overall draft pick had to give up on his olympic dreams of swimming due to his fear of sharks",
                    answer: "Tim Duncan"
                },
                {
                    value: 1000,
                    question: "Michael Jordan retired from basketball and spent 1994 playing with this Double-A minor league team",
                    answer: "Birmingham Barons"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            title: "Because We're Well Rounded",
            questions: [
                {
                    value: 200,
                    question: "In 1939, Germany invaded this country to start World War II",
                    answer: "Poland"
                },
                {
                    value: 400,
                    question: "This 1994 film featuring Tom Hanks won 45 awards and was the top grossing film of the year",
                    answer: "Forrest Gump"
                },
                {
                    value: 600,
                    question: "This Shakespeare play features the opening line 'To Be or Not To Be'",
                    answer: "Hamlet"
                },
                {
                    value: 800,
                    question: "What two countries are separated by the Bering straight",
                    answer: "USA and Russia"
                },
                {
                    value: 1000,
                    question: "What is the sixth element in the periodic table",
                    answer: "Carbon"
                }
            ]
        }
    ],
    finalJeopardy: {
        title : 'UNC vs Duke',
        question: {
            value: 0,
            question: "This year, Duke freshman Wendell Moore scored a buzzer beater as time expired to beat UNC. Who was the last player to hit a game-winning buzzer beater in the Duke/UNC rivalry",
            answer: "Austin Rivers in 2012"
        }
    }
};
